# BELLA SONG

E: yatingsong7@gmail.com PH: 0450408717 75 Drummond Street, Carlton 3053

#### **OBJECTIVE**

A hard-working IT graduate looking for a software developing job, where to apply my halfyear software developing experience on web and mobile application and two-year degree knowledge. Strong understanding of full-stack development, software management and ability to perform well in a team.

CSS

### **SKILLS**

- React.js
- HTML

JavaScript

- Node.js
- SQL

Java

- C#
- .NET
- Google Firebase

MongoDB

OOP

- Quick learning
- Teamwork
- Project management
- Time management
- Communication
- Problem solving

#### **WORK HISTORY**

**Software Developer** | JPS Health and Fitness, Melbourne (03/2022 – 06/2022 Capstone placement)

03/2022 - Current

- Implement real-time text and voice chat functions for Web and Mobile applications using React and Google Firestore
- Create APIs on backend using Node.js and retrieve user data from MySQL
- Take Responsible for UI design to ensure compatibility with existing applications
- · Communicate with IT team to fix bugs and do functional tests
- · Design Firestore database structure, analyze usage and potential bills
- Collaborate with development team of 4; Report and demo project weekly
- Maintain documentation using Agile and Scrum in response to new requirements

#### **Achievements**

- · As the project leader, led team to be the best of 12 teams in Capstone
- · Designed UI that followed market conventions and also meets customized needs
- Developed database that reduces CRUD times, saves money and increases efficiency

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Personal Portfolio

- · HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JQuery
- Built responsive animated page; includes resume download and project showcase

#### **Online Banking System**

- C#, .NET Core 5.0, CSHTML, Azure SQL
- Built REST API and 3-layer application; Used EF Core framework for DB operations; Implemented scheduled bill payment function by BackgroundService

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Master of Information Technology**

RMIT University, Australia, 2020-2022

The Complete 2022 Web Development Bootcamp

Udemy, online

The Complete React Developer in 2022 (Redux, Hooks, GraphQL) Udemy, online

References available upon request